MURTAZA DAWOODJEEWALA

Tech Enthusiast | Frontend Developer | Graphic Designer

+91 8208266645 @ murtazadawoodjee.connect@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/murtaza-dawoodjee Portfolio Github



SUMMARY

I am a tech enthusiast pursuing a career in technology, especially in frontend web development. With a passion for graphic design and UI/UX, I've cofounded a graphic design company and gained experience in IT administration. My technical skillset includes HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and various programming languages and frameworks

EXPERIENCE

Co-founder

MSquare Graphix

= 2022 - Present

A graphic design company focused on providing creative solutions

- •Co-founded the graphic design company MSquare Graphix
- •Involved in various graphic design projects

IT Admin Intern

BGI

= 2024 - Present

A non-profit organization engaged in community activities

•Working as an IT admin Intern in BGI, an NGO run by The Dawoodi Bohra Community

IT Intern

Anjuman e Kalimi A Dawoodi Bohra Jamaat

2024 - Present

An organization that serves the Dawoodi Bohra community

•Full-time Intern in Anjuman e Kalimi A Dawoodi Bohra Jamaat

EDUCATION

Bachelor Of Computer Application Medi-Caps University

Higher Secondary (12th)

St. Joseph's Convent Sr. Sec. School

• Ratlam, India

Senior Secondary (10th)

St. Joseph's Convent Sr. Sec. School

• Ratlam, India

KEY ACHIEVEMENTS

Entrepreneurship and Community Engagement

Co-founding a graphic design company and contributing to meaningful community projects in the field of technology and design

SKILLS

AWS C/C++ CSS EC₂ GCP GitHub HTML Java Gmail JavaScript Numpy Python React S3 Tailwind Android XAMPP

PROJECTS

Netflix Home Page

A Personal project replicating Netflix Home Page

- •Technologies used: HTML, CSS, **JavaScript**
- Project Link : Netflix Home Page

Weather App

A web-based application used to determine Weather using API

- Technologies used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Project Link: Weather App

RECIPIX

A Full fledged Web Application for Recipe Management & Recipe Viewing

- Technologies used: JavaScript, PHP, SQL, React, Lottie Files, Toastify, MySQL, XAMPP
- Project Link : Recipix